It was the electoral movement in the United States in 2016.
After that, the concept has begun to mean pretty much anything.
It is used for rumors, propaganda, poor journalism, misunderstanding.
-Everything can be described as fake news.
-It is a very specific concept.
People say fake news, so you don't know what they mean.
It's almost like a belligerent: "What you said is fake news."
Or: "You are fake news."
It sounds like something we can do in the program.
All kinds of fake news.
-Good idea, but first some coffee!
-Or energy drink!
Just wait.
Honey, your favorite star makes uninhibited advertising, but for you over 16.
If you want to party or plug all night, you should drink ---.
That a person is involved in something does not have to say what the whole looks like.
After all, a testimony can color a very many picture of the truth.
One has to ask how common and representative phenomenon is?
Just.
Much like "Tafsar Day" which was a few weeks ago.
It was alleged that there were calls in social media, on tiktok-
-"Challenges" that guys would paw on girls on the big "pawing day".
It seems to start with the police warned of "Tafsardag".
The big spread of "Tafsardag" came late.
It's disgusting.
It's good if parents talk to their children about it.
This is the problem:
-For the police, newspapers, the school has talked about it.
One has to weigh the balance between worrying or warning of something-
-What is a phenomenon for real.
We talked about that in previous programs.
There is a risk of a "copy cat" effect.
When someone does stupidity or it is talked about it-
-Tris it to inspire people to do stupidity.
Was it a joke from the beginning?
Would just a few idiots do it?
Was it big or small?
We do not know that about "Tafsardag".
We must be clear that abuse must be reported to the police.
If things happen at people's schools, they should tell you about it.
If we pick it up.
When someone has something to gain on it purely political-
-Then you can expect them to look for individual examples-
-To get this point.
It doesn't just have to be political actors or groups-
-What may be states that want to promote their own purposes.
On Russian state television last month, AstraZenecas vaccine-
-When an APVaccine and is portrayed as dangerous.
A study from the United States says the same Russian troll-
— which is suspected to have affected the election result in 2016-
-Have tried to fire on a debate about how safe vaccines are.
Sometimes even states use magic factories and armies of bottoms.
It is not dangerous if you stick to the daily intake.
Then we have the fraudsters who find different types of scams-
-To access personal data.
A man called my mom.
He said he called from the Public Health Authority-
-And had found her through infection tracking.
He would send mouth guard-
-And she just needed to verify that she is she.
Fraudsters try to find weaknesses.
They are looking for man who does not know they exist.
They try to get over personal information, money.
This can happen in many different ways.
They can send sms, messenger-
-dm, anyway!
Ideologically motivated.
It may be those who create and spread political propaganda.
It is not always wrong, but it may be busted-
-Or so something has been omitted to make a political point.
Foreign influence.
It is when states sit behind the fake accounts and pull the threads.
The goal is to promote their own purposes-
-And sometimes disturb or influence the debate in other countries.
You can release your pores and put yourself in focus with ---!
You don't have particles in the eyes-
-and unnecessary cascade effects around the temples.
Best of all?